警察学校Ⅵ
解救围城
"犯罪风潮袭卷城市"
学监 你巡视的时候一直在唱圣诞歌曲…
Proctor, you've been singingChristmas songs...
…已经连着五个小时了!
...for the entire five hoursof this stakeout.
圣诞节可还要等四个月呢!
Christmas is a good four months away.
你要是再敢哼一个字…
If you sing so much as one more note...
…我就毙了你
...I will shoot you.
接着唱…
Go ahead...
…给我过圣诞节
...make my Christmas.
长官 我们今天就到这儿了 好吗?
Sir, can we call it a day?
学监 我刚得到确切情报 威尔逊·海兹一伙…
I've got a very good tipthat the Wilson Heights Gang...
…要抢劫街对面的珠宝店
...is gonna rob the jewelry storeacross the street.
我想我们至少要等他们露面才能回家
I thought we might wait at least untilthey showed up before we call it a day.
- 没问题吧? - 是的 长官
- Is that okay with you? - Yes, sir.
我一般周日都要给我的侄女讲故事
I usually read the funniesto my niece on Sunday.
你明白吗
Don't you understand?
我花了一年的时间…
It took me a year to get transferred...
才从拉萨和他的那帮小坏蛋们身边调开
...away from Lassardand his band of misfits.
现在我有了自己的地盘我可不会让任何人给我捣乱
Now that I've got my own precinct,I'm not gonna let anyone screw with me.
我的地盘我说了算
It's my precinct.I make the rules.
我要是不说"行" 任何人连撒泡尿都不行!
No one takes so much as a leakwithout my say - so.
- 我的第六感告诉我… - 长官…
- I have a sixth sense. - Sir...
- 让我说完 我的第六… - 但是 长官!
- Let me finish. I have a sixth... - But, sir!
你能让我先说完吗?
Would you let me finish?
当有犯罪正在实施时 我的第六感会告诉我
I have a sixth sensewhen it comes to crime...
- 但是 长官! - 别打断我!
- But, sir! - Stop interrupting me!
当有犯罪正在实施时 我的第六感会告诉我
I have got a sixth sensewhen it comes to crime.
我的直觉告诉我这些犯罪活动…
My instincts tell me this crime wave...
…立马就会结束
...is about to come to an abrupt end.
嘿 你! 站住!
Hey, you! Hold it!
- 停下! - 不许动!
- Hold it! - Freeze!
哈里斯上尉!
Captain Harris!
你们在这干什么?
What are you doing here?
我们在巡逻 这是怎么回事?
Well, we're on a stakeout.What's all this about?
威尔逊·海兹又干坏事了
The Wilson Heights Gang struck again.
- 在哪? - 那儿 长官
- Where? - There, sir.
在您身后
Right behind you.
你们什么时候到这的 长官?
When did you get here, sir?
- 嗯 我们… - 我们在这儿呆了五个小时了
- Well, we... - We've been here five hours.
- 噢 胡说 - 抢劫的时候你们一直在这儿?
- Shut up, Proctor. - You were here during the robbery?
- 当然不在
- Of course not. - Yes, we were, sir.
- 是的 我们在这儿 长官 他们几分钟前跑了 - 闭嘴!
- They came a few minutes ago. - Shut up.
- 我本来要跟您说的 - 闭嘴!
- I tried to tell you. - Shut up.
- 哪道您不记得吗? 在车里 - 闭嘴、闭嘴、闭嘴!
- Don't you remember? Inside the car. - Shut up. Shut up. Shut up!
"威尔逊·海兹再施犯罪给哈里斯上尉挂上尾巴"
噢 先生们…
Oh, gentlemen...
…你们两周前对我发过誓要抓住这伙人的!
...you promised me you would havethis gang in custody two weeks ago!
相反 他们让我们看上去就像一帮…哦…
Instead, they're making us looklike a bunch of... Uh...
…噢 可笑的…
Oh, the ones that are very funny.
…海王抓住了他们把我的叉…傻瓜!
The kings have them.Bring me my f... Fools!
- 弄得我们就像傻瓜! - 市长先生 我…
- Making us look like fools! - Mr. Mayor, I...
- 我可以向您保证… - 歇着吧!
- I can assure you... - Save it.
人们都害怕了 都跑别处做生意了
People are afraid. They're takingtheir business elsewhere.
商人们都围攻我! 一些重要的…
The merchants are all over me.Some very important...
那些…这里再没有钱可挣了!
The ones that...Feathers are being ruffled here.
现在州长也插手了!
And now the governor is involved!
他要我们赶紧把犯罪压制下去
He wants this crime wavestopped immediately.
他还指定了一个特派小组…
And he is sending in a special team...
…来检查…呃…制止犯罪的情况
...to see that the crime wave is stopped.
市长大人…
Mr. Mayor, Your Honor...
我想哈里斯上尉想说的是…
I think what Captain Harrisis trying to say...
…他的部门将对所得到的帮助
...is his department will appreciate...
- 感激不尽 - 是的 很好 谢谢
...all the help it can get. - Yes. Good. Thank you.
但基于哈里斯上尉可能再会失误…
But due to the possibility of a leakin Captain Harris' department...
…州长从本区之外挑选了一个小队
...the governor chose a teamoutside the precinct.
他确定他们会把这些无赖带到…
He feels sure that they will bringthese scoundrels to the...
你知道 法庭之类的地方去
You know, to the court thing.
正义! 让他们受到正义的审判!
Justice! Bring them to justice.
噢 对不起
Oh, excuse me.
喂 是噢 请他进来 是的
Hello. Yeah.Oh, send him in, yes.
谢谢 米粒儿
Thank you, Midge.
哈里斯上尉 赫斯特局长…
Captain Harris, Commissioner Hurst...
…我想你肯定认识…拉萨指挥官
...I'm sure you knowCommandant Lassard.
谢谢 米粒儿
Thank you, Midge.
你…我要确认一下我的理解
You... Let me make sureI understand this.
你将要和我一起工作
You are going to be working with me.
肩并肩地工作!
Side by side.
我跟你一样高兴
I feel just the same.
我们非常高兴能得到您的携助 拉萨指挥官
We're very happy to have you with us,Commandant Lassard.
我很确定 很确定…
I am sure, sure...
…你会帮我们把这些坏蛋赶尽杀绝
...that you will help us tree these swine.
市长大人 我有很多优秀的人选
Your Honor, I have just the menfor the job.
噢!
Oh!
嘿 谁愿意跟我一对一地来一场?
Now, who wants to go one - on - one?
不
No.
抬头 伙计们!
Heads up, people!
是布拉德 他真是个孩子
It's Brad. He's such a child.
- 你好 - 真高兴再见到你
- Hello. - Nice seeing you again.
- 你看上去真可爱 - 谢谢
- You look lovely. - Thank you.
- 一定记得给我打电话 我们一起共进午餐 - 好的
- Do call sometime, we'll have lunch. - I will.
- 你好 亲爱的! - 你好
- Hello, dear. - Hello.
- 嗨 斯坦威克夫人 - 嗨 琼斯
- Hi, Mrs. Stanwyck. - Hi, Jonesy.
你以前见过这样一群醉鬼吗?
Did you ever see such a bunch of stiffs?
伊莱恩 你精神真棒!
Elaine, exceptional event.
瞧着
Watch this.
他到底在做什么?
What on earth is he doing?
谢谢 伙计
Thanks, pal.
这会让我下个小时轻松许多
That should get methrough the next hour.
对不起
Excuse me.
- 你认为你在做什么? - 我是警察 我的职责是…
- What do you think you're doing? - I'm a police officer. It's my duty...
- 你知不知道我是谁? - 不 但我想…
- Do you have any idea who I am? - No, but I wanted to...
我是温德尔·皮·法斯沃斯
I'm Wendell P. Farnsworth.
我姐夫是议员 我是你们指挥官的私人朋友
My brother - in - law's a councilman, I'm apersonal friend of the watch commander.
所以我想让我们忘记这小小的误解
So I suggest we forget all aboutthis little misunderstanding.
- 懂我的意思吗? - 但你的车停在红色区域里
- Got me? - But you were parked in a red zone.
- 我必须给你开罚单… - 让我跟你说清楚 小丫头
- I have to give you a ticket... - Let me make it clear to you, girl.
现在 从这给我滚开…
Now, get out of here...
…不然我就把你揍扁…
...before I have you busted down...
…让你爬不起来!
...to crossing guard.
- 真棒! - 让她长长见识!
- All right. - You told her.
你们知道该怎么对待苦力了吧? 懂了吗?
You got to know how to handle peons,you know what I mean?
又什么事?
What now?
- 这是什么? - 罪证：泊车在红色区域…
- What's this? - Citations for parking in a red zone...
…离路边距离超过18英寸挡住消防栓…
...more than 18 inches from the curb,blocking a fire hydrant...
…驾照过期 无保险杠 乱丢垃圾 恶意袭警…
...expired registration, no front plate,littering, attempt to extort an officer...
…故意撕毁法院传票
...and willfully destroyinga court summons.
噢 不! 我的车!
Oh, no! My car!
你可以到警局去提你的车当然是在交了罚金之后 小子!
You can pick it up at the police impoundafter you pay for your citations, boy!
"房屋及地基雷区保护"
- 早上好 儿子 - 早上好 爸爸
- Morning, son. - Morning, Dad.
起居室里可能发生211
Possible 211 in progressin the living room.
- 我们需不需要救援? - 不 我们应付的了
- Shall we call for backup? - No. We can handle it.
- 外公? - 爸爸?
- Grandpa. - Dad.
我就拿了一个恶心的三明治
All I took is a lousy sandwich.
早上好 欢迎大家来到威尔逊·海兹的地盘
Good morning and welcometo the Wilson Heights Division.
现在 开始干活吧!
Now, let's get to work.
这伙人比我们先到一步
This gang has been one stepahead of us.
现在州长觉得我们部门里
Now, the governor feels that someonein this department...
有人泄露了消息
...may be leaking.
以防万一…
To guard against that possibility...
…只有这间屋子里的人知道这个计划
...only the people in this roomwill know our plans.
现在 这些板子上的内容…
Now, these boards...
…是我们关于这些抢劫
...carry the only information we have...
所掌握的全部信息
...about these robberies.
我们…哈里斯上尉?
We...Captain Harris?
指挥官谢谢 拉萨指挥官
Commandant.Thank you, Commandant Lassard.
尽管我们有很多的目击证人…
Though we have dozensof eyewitnesses...
…但没有人能从我们的照片目录中将他们指认出来
...no one has been able to identifyany of these men from our mug books.
我们因此只能断定…
We can only assume therefore...
…他们没有犯罪纪录三组未经确认的指纹…
...they have no police records.Three sets of unidentified fingerprints...
…出现在每一个犯罪现场
...have been found at each crime scene.
但我们的指纹纪录中没有查到相关信息
But running them through our recordshas also drawn us a blank.
不管这些作恶者是谁 他们肯定是行家
Whoever these perpetrators are,they're pros.
但他们犯了一个致命的错误
But they have made one fatal mistake.
他们选择了…
They chose...
…我的地盘
...my precinct.
对! 没错! 是的!
Yeah! Yeah! All right! All right!
- 立正! - 请坐
- Ten - hut! - Be seated.
- 长官 我刚通知了他们 - 谢谢 哈里斯上尉
- I've been briefing the men, sir. - Thank you, Captain Harris.
现在 在这…
Now, in the...
- 长官 你还好吧? - 滚开!
- Sir, are you okay? - Get away!
在既不存在指纹和照片纪录的情况下…
In the absence of identifiablefingerprints and photographs...
…我们只能依赖旧有的但有效的巡侦办法了
...we're gonna have to relyon good old - fashioned police work.
拉萨指挥官 我想您说过您有个七人小队
Commandant, I thought you saidyou had a seven - man team.
是的 局长
I do, commissioner.
- 早上好! - 哎哟!
- Morning. - Ow!
- 嗨! - 早上好!
- Hi, there. - Morning.
- 你好 - 嘿
- Hello. - Hey.
天气不错
Nice day.
- 早上好 - 嗨
- Morning. - Hi.
回来真好
It's good to be back.
先生们 我想你们都认识法克勒中士
Gentlemen, you all knowSergeant Fackler.
- 赫斯特局长 - 你好 中士
- Commissioner Hurst. - Hello there, sergeant.
现在我们人都齐了…
Now that our team is complete...
…我知道我们很快就会打垮敌人
...I know we shall soontriumph over our enemies.
嗨 拉维恩 高塔!
Hi. Laverne. Hightower.
- 嗨 我是尼克 - 你好
- Hi, I'm Nick. - Hello.
你好…哎哟!
How do you...?Whoops!
法克勒 拿拖把来!
Fackler, get a mop!
拖把
A mop.
疏散!
Evacuate!
从屋子里撤出去!
Evacuate this room now!
这出场可真够漂亮的
This is not a good combination.
抢劫!
Fire in the hole.
好了 好了 我们走快点儿!
Come on, come on. Let's go.Hurry up.
你家在哪里?
Where you from originally?
嗯哼
Hm - mm.
你是头儿吗?
You the president?
- 有钥匙吗? - 没有
- You got the key for this? - No.
好吧
Okay.
他把你从座位上举起来?
He lifted you out of your chair?
嗯 越过桌子来到地下室里
And across my desk,and he carried me into the vault.
对不起
Excuse me.
对不起 他跑了 带着大约19万美元
Excuse me. He got awaywith approximately $ 190,000.
谢谢
Thank you.
太谢谢你了
嗯 有什么建议吗?
Well, suggestions?
我建议我们带着画像
I suggest we canvass...
彻底搜查整个地区
Canvass the entire areawith our modified police - artist sketches.
天知道 也许我们会很幸运
Who knows, we might get lucky.
街上的消息也许会有用
- The word... - Word on the street might help.
听听线人们的消息 或许再派几个密探
Listen to the stoolies,maybe put a few men undercover.
嗯 拉萨指挥官?
Well, Commandant Lassard?
街上的消息…
The word on the street...
…也许会给我们点线索
...might give us a clue.
我想这话我刚刚说完
I think I just said that.
到了他这个年纪 记性已经不顶用了
At his age, the memory comes and goes.
噢!
Whoops!
嘿 黛比 瞧瞧这个
Hey, Debbie, take a look at this.
谢谢 道格拉斯
Thank you, Douglas.
嗯 至少他们没把全部的钱弄走 不是吗?
Well, at least they didn't getall the money, huh?
他们很聪明没拿这个这是个爆炸染色包
They were too smart to take this.It's an exploding dye pack.
它只要一被拿出银行就会爆炸
It's activated when you take it outof the bank.
如果你还想其它的什么事 给哈里斯上尉打电话
If you remember anything else at all,call Captain Harris.
- 长官… - 你在这儿干什么 中士?
- Sir... - What are you doing there, sergeant?
长官 我找到了抢匪丢的钱
Sir, I found money the gang dropped.
- 我想我该把这个拿去给局长 - 很好 我来拿
- Thought I'd take it to the commissioner. - That's all right, I'll take it.
- 我想这抢劫… - 这就成了
- I think a job... - That will be all.
好的好的
Alrighty.
- 学监 - 是 长官
- Proctor. - Yes, sir.
给我盯着点这些人
Keep an eye on these people.
局长
Commissioner.
- 什么事 哈里斯上尉? - 已经没事了
- Yes, Captain Harris. - It wasn't important.
尼克 谢谢 克拉克
Nick. Thanks, Clarke.
我想我找到了什么 请继续
I think we got something here.Go ahead.
- 那个大个… - 坚持住 上尉!
- The big guy... - Hang on, captain!
正在开保险箱
Was breaking openthe safety - deposit boxes.
拿枪的那个人跟他们说别这样然后他们吵起来了
The man with the guns told him not to,and then they argued.
告诉他那家伙说了什么
Tell him what the guy said.
那个大个说："为什么不? "
The big guy said, "Why not?"
拿枪的人说："因为抢这东西他不付我们钱"
The guy with the gun said, "Becausethat's not what we're being paid for."
他们是被雇来的
They're just hired help.
肯定有人计划的这场抢劫
There must be somebody planningthe robberies.
有人在幕后操纵
Somebody behind the scenes.
一个策划者
A mastermind.
- 老大 - 是的
- Ace. - Yeah.
你想这个老板会是谁?
Who do you think the boss really is?
我不知道 但不管他是谁…
I don't know, but whoever he is...
…他肯定有很优越的社会关系
...he's certainly well - connected. - Yeah.
没错 警察一有动静我们就会知道
We know what the cops will dobefore they do.
- 了不起吧? - 嘿
- Ain't it something? - Hey.
瞧 公牛
Check out Ox.
公牛 五分钟 时间到了你赢了
Ox, five minutes, your time's up.You win the bet.
给你钱
You gotta pay him.
我告诉过你
I told you.
下午好 先生们
Good afternoon, gentlemen.
我非常高兴地告诉你们…
I am pleased to say...
我的计划进行的非常完美
...my plan is proceeding perfectly.
我们一起制造了这座城市
Together, we have brought fortha wave of crime...
前所未闻的犯罪浪潮
...such as this city has never known.
只要一提到我们的名字
Every mind is filled with dread.
所有人心中都充满了恐惧
Every fear bears our name.
只要再来几次…
Only a few more robberies...
…制造混乱的时机就成熟了
...and all will be ripefor Operation Chaos.
到处都充满了恐慌、混乱与毁灭
There will be panic, anarchy, destruction.
我们要让这座城市给我们下跪!
We shall bring this city to its knees.
很有趣 但我们以前谈过这个 不是吗?
Very funny. But we've talkedabout this before, haven 't we?
噢 是的
Oh, yes.
拿过来
Bring them up here.
快点
Come on.
等一切结束的时候你会拿回它们的
You can have them backat the end of the crime wave.
尊敬的阁下大人…
With all due respect, Your Reverence...
…拉萨的手下就是一些没本事的笨蛋…
...Lassard's peopleare incompetent fools...
…他们只会把一切搞得团团糟
...who are going to screw upthis whole investigation.
我当然了解你的困难
I certainly appreciateyour difficulty, captain.
我的意思是 我要你监督
I mean, after all,I want these swine captured...
这些笨猪的一举一动
...every bit as much as you do.
我该怎么办? 我的手…
What can I do? My hands are...
这东西… 噢!
The thing... Oh!
- 带着绳子 - 被绑着
- With the ropes. - Tied.
当我需要你帮助的时候 哈里斯上尉相信我 我肯定会找你的
When I want your help, Captain Harris,you may rest assured, I will ask for it.
这必竟是局长的秀场 对吧? 我是说 我的手被绑着
After all, this is the governor's show,isn't it? I mean, my hands are tied.
不管怎样…
However...
…如果你可以找到任何可以证明…
...if you should find any evidence...
…拉萨和他的手下…
...proving that Lassard and his men...
…在以各种方式破坏调查的证据…
...are hurting the investigationin any way...
喔! 哇!
Choo - choo - choo - choo,woo - woo.
…我也将别无选择 只能直接去找局长…
...I would have no choicebut to go right to the governor...
…把他们从这赶走
...and have them removed from the case.
我希望您能第三次连任 长官大人
I wish you could run for a third term,Your Honor.
- 我非常愿意再投您一票 - 哎哟
- I would love to vote for you again. - Ow.
- 我也是 - 谢谢你们给我信心
- Me too. - Thank you for that vote of confidence.
我这个下午很忙 所以如果你们不介意…
Now, I'm very busy this afternoon.So if you don't mind...
…那就祝你们拥有美好的…
...have a nice...
…东西 - 您也是 长官大人
...thingy. - And you too, Your Honor.
你再敢碰别的东西在我们走之前…
Don't you touch another thing.Before we leave...
请允许我就您那些神话般的
...please allow me the privilegeto congratulate you...
船模收藏表示祝贺
...on your fabulous collectionof model ships.
啊 谢谢 这些都是我亲手制作的
Ah. Thank you.Built them all myself.
当然 这是一种心甘情愿的劳作
Of course, it's a labor of love.
嗯 你手上拿着的那个模型送你了
Now, take that one you're holding nowin your hands.
我在这小宝贝儿的身上花了一年的时间
I've spent a year on that little baby.
噢! 噢!
Oh! Oh!
噢! 不!
Oh, no!
我能修好它
I can fix it.
- 噢! - 我会花整个周末的时间
- Oh. - I've got the whole weekend.
我很善长木工活
I'm very good with wood.
它会好起来的
It's okay.
相信我
Trust me.
噢!
Oh!
赫斯特局长说的对
Commissioner Hurst is right.
我们必须开始基础的警察调查
We must startwith basic police investigation.
我们应该把这些…
We shall circulate these sketches...
由我们非常非常有天赋的警察画像师绘制的画像散发出去
...by our very, very talented police artist.
然后很多很多的子弹就会向我们飞来
We shall come up with many,many leads.
对不起 我迟到了
Sorry I'm late.
我错过什么了吗?
Did I miss anything?
- 说吧 尼克 - 长官 我得到了一条消息…
- Yes, Nick. - Sir, we got a tip...
…罪犯在联合大楼里有个聚点儿
...that an office at the Union Towersis being used by the mob.
我想派两个秘密警官到那儿去…
I think sending twoundercover officers...
…也许会给我们机会使案件更容易侦破
...to this location may give us the breakthat'll crack this case wide open.
- 琼斯中士和我… - 我来分配任务 中士
- Sergeant Jones and myself... - I'll handle this assignment, sergeant.
我可不认为这样的任务适合你的人…
I don't think an assignment like thisis appropriate for a man of your...
胡说 中士
Nonsense, sergeant.
你还尿床的时候我就在破案了
I was handling undercover caseswhen you were still trick - or - treating.
联合高楼的秘密任务
We'll have Captain Harrisand Lieutenant Proctor...
将由哈里斯上尉和学监中尉来负责
...take the undercover assignmentat the Union Towers building.
- 秘密任务绝对让人兴奋 - 闭嘴 学监
- Undercover work is sure exciting. - Shut up, Proctor.
学监 我们应该隐藏起来
Proctor, we're supposed tobe undercover.
我知道 我正试着给他们来个措手不及
I know, I was trying to throw themoff guard.
- 先把窗户擦干净 - 长官
- Just wash the windows. - Sir.
谢谢 长官
Thank you, sir.
我想我们应该谈一谈伙计们下一步该做什么
I think we need to talkabout what The Gang is gonna do next.
没错 下次活可是关键的一次
Yeah. This next job is gonna bethe crucial one.
而且会…
It's gonna be...
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
长官 如果你不正确的使用橡胶扫帚的话窗户上会留下印子的
Sir, if you don't squeegee thesewindows properly, it leaves streaks.
- 擦擦那 - 噢
- Squeegee over there. - Oh.
谢谢你 中士
Thank you, sergeant.
这是我小时候常来的俱乐部来吧
This used to be my boys' club.Come on.
它变了很多
It really has changed.
抱歉打扰一下…
Pardon the intrusion...
…这是些警方的罪犯画像 请您看一下 我将万分感谢
...but I have these police sketchesI'd appreciate you looking at.
嗯 当然
Well, certainly, officer.
但首先 我们为什么不边说话边打几局球呢 啊?
But first, why don't we shoot a coupleof friendly games while we talk, huh?
再好不过了
Splendid.
这里的气氛总是很友好
This always was a friendly neighborhood.
- 小子 过来! - 我要…
- Come here, son. - I'II...
瞧着 我要把这个老东西的家底儿都赢光
Watch this. I'm gonna hustle this old fartfor everything he owns.
介意我问您一些问题吗?
Do you mind if I ask youa few questions?
- 说吧 你先开球 - 好的
- Let's shoot first. - Okay.
拿着这个
Hold this.
拿着
- 你知道 我不擅长运动 - 嘿 警官!
- I'm not good with sports, you know. - Hey, sarge.
这是…我会试试
This is...I'll try.
- 我先来 - 好! 好!
- I'll go first. - Yeah, yeah.
噢 好了 你们都累了 我再来一遍 很好
That's okay if you guys are tired,I'll shoot again. This is nice.
呀!
Jeez.
进啦!
That'll do it.
你想知道什么?
What would you like to know?
你懂我的意思
You know what I'm saying, B
哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈
OG
尖叫会伤害我的听力人们惊慌失措 混乱在即
Screaming almost damaged my earsThe people running in fear
喧嚣、吵闹 一切都被毁灭
The hour to devour is nearPandemonium, chaos, total destruction
悲剧带来了令人不安的诱惑
Tragedy portrays an eerie seduction
枪战、群殴、刀光剑影
Gunshots, fistfights, even knives
人们受伤、丢掉性命
People getting hurtOthers losing their lives
毫无疑问 你无法否认
No doubt about itAnd you can 't deny it
争吵的原因会带来暴动
What started as a quarrelTurned into a riot
尸横遍野
Bodies laid out all over the ground
血流满地
Blood spattered everywhere
人心沮丧城中的少年投贼卖友
People getting beat downInner city juvie going out with a bang
嗨 我们是…
Hi, we're...
你能告诉我们…
Could you tell us...?
你的节奏让我摇摆
Your beat kept me movingFrom right to left
你的音乐 怎么说 真叫棒
Your rap is, how you say, real def
但我们需要你们的帮助
But we need some helpAnd some information
告诉我们威尔逊·海兹的藏身之处
About the gangsIn the Wilson Heights situation
你知道吗 她是个说唱歌手兼警察
What do you know?She's a rapper and a cop
所有人都爱说唱 为什么要停呢?
Man, everybody's rappingWhere will it stop
人们总对说唱抱怨不断
People give rap a whole lot of beef
但现在没牙的老人们也为之疯狂
But now old folks are rappingWithout no teeth
我们正谈论一伙四处作恶的强贼
We're rapping about gangsThat go around banging
抢劫、偷盗、射杀无辜到处游荡、破坏环境
Robbing, stealing, shootingHanging on corners, polluting the nature
留下你的电话有消息我们会去汇报
So give me your numberIn case we get some information
我保证
- Word - We believe you guys
我们相信你们 所以不再争论但如果你们撒谎
We won 't dispute youBut if you're lying to us
我们会回来把你们干掉我也保证
We'll come back and shoot youWord
这些家伙可是些大人物
These guys are gonna be big.
没错 那现在这些家伙们在哪?
Yeah. So where's The Gangliving these days?
哈里斯上尉?
Captain Harris?
噢 该死!
Shit. Ah!
噢 上帝呀!
Oh, God!
噢 我帮助过穷人! 噢 帮帮我 学监!
I'll feed the poor! Oh, please, help me!
- 噢 圣母快救救我! - 好的 好的
- Oh, please, help me! - Okay. Okay.
好了 好了
Okay.
好了 你能成的!
Okay, you can do it!
谢谢你 学监 我永远也不会忘记…
Thank you, Proctor! I'll never forget...
别管裤子 先救你自己 长官!
Don't worry about the pants!Save yourself, sir!
神啊 别让我死啊!
God, please don't let me die.
我还年轻 求求你…
I'm so young. Please...
上帝 我会帮助无家可归的人 还有穷苦的人…
- God, I'll help the homeless!I'll feed the poor.
我会乖乖的…
Oh, I'll be so good.
我说话算话 我真的说话算话!
I mean it. I really, really mean it!
谢谢你所做的一切 哈里斯上尉
Thank you for your contribution,Captain Harris.
啊喔! 别、别让我死!
Please, don 't let me die!
我会…
I'm...
嗯 看起来…
Well, it would seem...
…我们旧有的工作方法捆住了我们的手脚
...that all our old - fashioned police workhas netted us zip.
我们不清楚这些人的身份
We don't know who these men are.
不知道他们下一步的目标
We don't know where they're goingto strike next.
- 说吧 中士 - 嗯 也许我们知道 长官
- Yes, sergeant. - Well, maybe we do, sir.
也许下次他们会在我们希望的地方出现
Maybe they'll strikeexactly where we want them to.
没错
Right.
"无价之宝津巴布韦钻石明日抵达
威尔逊·海兹博物馆宝石展更添光彩"
诱饵越好陷阱才会越有效
A trap is only as goodas the bait you use.
红色领袖呼叫周边 报告你处的情况
Red Leader to perimeter. Report.
一号检查站 一切正常
Checkpoint One. Nothing here.
你好 小家伙我打赌给你带了好东西
Well, hello there, little fellow.Bet I got something for you.
好了 来吧
All right. Here we go.
瞧着 我来给你喝点好喝的牛奶
Look at this. See, I'm gonna get yousome good milk.
这 喝吧
Here. There you go.
这事就咱俩知道 好吗?
Let's just keep thisbetween me and you. Okay?
- 二号检查站? - 二号收到 未见异常
- Checkpoint Two? - Checkpoint Two. Negative.
到机场 快点 我很急
Airport. I'm in a hurry.
去坐公交
Take the bus.
我不想坐公交我要坐你的车 快点 踩油门吧!
I don't wanna take the bus.I wanna take your cab. Now, step on it.
要么坐公交要么就尝尝这个下车 先生!
You'll take the bus and like it.Now, mister!
我们先共进晚餐 然后他带我去了他的住处
He took me to dinner, then to his place.
到了之后两分钟 他说：
And we've been there all of two minuteswhen he says:
"噢 宝贝儿 你真漂亮来点葡萄酒怎么样? "
"Oh, baby, you're so fine.How about some wine?"
- 五号 你在吗? - 你相信吗…
- Checkpoint Five. Are you there? - Can you believe...?
噢 等会儿
Just a minute, Di.
五号检查站 这很寂静
Checkpoint Five. All quiet here.
然后我看着他 对他说…
So then I look at him, and I say...
周围怎么样 三号?
What's happening, Checkpoint Three?
三号 一切正常
Checkpoint Three. Nothing unusual here.
四号报告
Checkpoint Four, report.
四号 是的 毫无敌情
Checkpoint Four. Yeah, all clear.
感谢您呼叫K - D - O - Z K - Doz检查站 一切正常
Thank you for calling K - D - O - Z. K - Doz,the station where nothing happens.
好啦 注意 我相信我们随时都会被抢的
Come on, now, chin up.I'm sure we'll get robbed any minute.
但愿 但愿
Promises, promises.
就在这 学监 当设好这个陷阱了之后…
Right here, Proctor.When this trap is sprung...
…抢劫就会在这发生而我就在这
...right here is where the action will be.And I will be right in the middle of it.
这也是为什么我要坚持把这项任务揽到自己怀里的原因
This is why I insistedthat I be given this assignment.
您真是明白如何仗屎欺人
You sure know howto throw your fat around, sir.
仗势欺人 学监!
That's weight, Proctor.
- 仗势! - 噢 仗势
- Weight. - Oh, weight.
- 那是什么? - 我不知道 长官
- What's that? - I don't know, sir.
他们就在外面 学监 我能感觉得到
They're out there, Proctor. I feel it.
他们随时都会袭击这辆卡车我们的人马上就赶到…
They'll attack this truck,our men will move in...
…然后我就会亲手制止威尔逊·海兹一伙
...and I will personally put an endto the Wilson Heights Gang.
简单极了 真的
It's quite simple, really.
- 您觉得我们会受到赞扬吗 长官? - 奖章?
- Do you think we'll get commendations? - Medals?
他们会把整个城市交给我
They'll give me the key to the city.
首先 每天六点的新闻会有我的讲话
First, I'll address the cityon the 6:00 news.
"这座城市已经安全了 为您服务是我的荣耀" 等等等等
"The city is safe. It was my privilegeto serve you," et cetera.
- 长官 - 我想还会有有秩序的游行
- Sir. - I think maybe a parade is in order.
- 长官 - 当然我还会成为大元帅
- Sir. - I'll be the grand marshal, of course.
我还不得不面对所有谈话节目的邀请
I'll have to face all the talk - show offers.
- 长官! - 怎么了 学监?
- Sir! - What is it, Proctor?
救命! 把我拉上去!
Help! Pull me up!
救命! 不! 不!
Help! No! No!
停车! 停车!
Halt! Halt!
- 停车! 停车! - 救命!
- Halt! Halt! - Help!
他们听不见 长官
They can't hear me, sir.
长官 跑步确实是非常棒的有氧运动
Sir, running really is the best formof aerobic exercise.
感觉不好吗?
Is it bad?
他们知道 他们什么都知道
They knew. They knew all about it.
肯定有人泄了密
Somebody had to tip them off.
- 但只有我们的队员们知道这个计划 - 不 埃里克叔叔…
- But only our team knew about the plan. - No, Uncle Eric...
…这个漏洞不在这一区域内
...the leak is not in the precinct.
…而在我们之中
It's one of us.
嗯 不过那时这确实看上去是个好计划
Well, it seemed likea good plan at the time.
噢 是的是的 一个好计划
Oh, yes, yes. A fine plan.
我们丢掉了价值连城的钻石…
We lose a priceless diamond...
…威尔逊·海兹制造了本世纪最大的犯罪…
...the Wilson Heights Gangpulls the crime of the century...
而我们就象一群笨蛋因为事实上是我们邀请他们来的
...and we look like a bunch of jerksbecause we practically invited them.
感谢您做的好事 拉萨中士
Do us a favor, Sergeant Lassard.
下次你再想出这样的好主意…
The next time you have a brilliant idea...
…求你了 留着自己使吧
...please, keep it to yourself.
屁眼儿!
Asshole!
现在 哈里斯上尉 如果你能坐下
But now, Captain Harris,if you'll take a seat.
也许换一个座位
Perhaps a different seat.
我们应该停止垂头丧气
We've got to stop feeling sorryfor ourselves.
到目前为止…
Now, so far...
…这伙人看上去似乎很偏执于在我们这一区域实行犯罪
...this gang seems to be confiningits robberies to our precinct.
- 发现什么了吗 尼克? - 不 不 我只是在记笔记
- You got something, Nick? - No, no. I'm just taking some notes.
打扰一下 哈里斯上尉 市长想立刻见你
Captain Harris, the mayor wantsto see you as soon as possible.
市长想见到我
The mayor would like to see me.
那好 别让市长等着了
Well, don't keep him waiting.
请原谅
If you'll excuse me.
学监!
Proctor!
我要一个完整的自动喷水灭火系统的报告
I want a complete reporton this sprinkler system.
- 喷水? - 喷水
- Sprinklers? - Sprinklers.
下午好 您好吗? 见到您真好 您好 您好
Good afternoon. How are you?So nice to see you. Hello. Hello.
欢迎到美国来 伟大的国家! 谢谢 非常感谢
Welcome to America. A great country.Thank you. Thank you very much.
7吗?
Seven?
哈里斯 不用麻烦了 不用起立
Harris. Don't bother to rise.
一大堆胶水 一点爱心都没有
A whole lot of glue,but not an ounce of love.
有什么进展吗 哈里斯上尉?
Have any progress to report,Captain Harris?
嗯 事实上 我恐怕没有什么我们的工作有些停滞
Well, actually, I'm afraid not, sir.We're at a bit of a standstill.
我们正重新审问所有的证人但这些 当然 只是一些基本程序
We are re - questioning all the witnesses,but that, of course, is basic procedure.
这不是我想听到的 哈里斯上尉
This is not what I want to hear,Captain Harris.
我想听到的是这些骗子已经被…
I wanna hear that these crookshave been...
- 那个 带上手铐叫… - 被捕!
- The thing when you put the cuffs on... - Caught!
- 被捕 很对 被捕 - 我正在努力 长官 我真的在努力!
- Caught. That's exactly right. Caught. - I'm trying, sir. I really am.
但有拉萨和他的人拖我的后腿 这真的不容易
But it's not easy with Lassardand his men slowing me down.
是的 装甲车的那件事 真是一团糟
Yes, that business with the armored car.That was a mess.
你还有什么其它的要报怨吗?
Do you have any other complaintsagainst them at all?
现在没有了 阁下大人
Not yet, Your Eminence.
但我知道拉萨和他的外甥正在策划着什么
But I know Lassard and his nepheware up to something.
- 我要查出来到底是什么! - 什么?
- And I am going to find out what! - What?
- 这就是我要查的 - 好吧 开始干吧!
- That's what I'm going to find out. - All right, let's get cracking!
- 是 长官! - 动起来!
- Yes, sir! - Let's get this case moving!
- 是 长官! - 去吧!
- Yes, sir! - Go!
是!
Yes, sir!
米粒儿 去给我查查看为什么哈里斯屁股上会有个凳子
Midge, find out why Harrishas got a chair on his ass.
呼!
Whoo!
行啦 尼克 我们从中午就到这儿了
Come on, Nick,we've been here since noon.
- 你还没告诉我们要做什么 - 瞧 你们应该相信我
- You haven't told us what we're doing. - Look, you guys just have to trust me.
- 能为您效劳吗 先生? - 那条项链非常引人注目
- May I help you, sir? - I got my eye on that necklace there.
嗯 它很漂亮 让我给您拿出来看看吗?
It is beautiful. Shall I show it to you?
不了 谢谢 我自己来拿
No, thank you. I'll get it myself.
行了 行了 保持安静
All right, all right, all right. Stay calm.
不好意思 把这弄乱了
Sorry about the mess.
嗯 现在 你把保险箱藏哪了?
Okay, now,where do you hide your safe?
- 准备好了叫我 - 在密室里 油画后面
- Call me when you're ready. - Back room, behind the painting.
十分感谢
Thank you.
谢谢
我们就耽误您几分钟
We'll just be a minute.
- 不好意思 借光 - 我不认识他们
- Excuse me, coming through. - I don't know them.
- 你怎么知道的? - 我也不明白…
- How'd you know? - I don't get it yet...
…不知道什么原因 抢劫是沿着旧的51路公交线路进行的
...but for some reason, the robberiesfollow the old 51 bus route.
- 回来! - 这是抢劫! 吼!
- Get back here! - Criminals, ho!
噢 混蛋!
Oh, crapola.
冲 学监!
Let's go, Proctor!
不许动 不许动! 你们被捕了 举起手来!
Freeze! Freeze!You're under arrest! Hands up!
哈里斯 你在火线之内 快让开!
Harris, you're in the line of fire.Get out of the way!
当然 你希望如此 是吗?
Sure, you'd like that, wouldn't you?
嗯 让我告诉你 拉萨中士
Well, let me tell you something,Sergeant Lassard.
我碰巧掌管这个地区而且我完美地…
I happen to be captain of this precinct,and I am perfectly...
快走 快走 学监!
Let's go, Proctor!
- 所有单位注意 发生抢劫 - 我手受伤了 快快快!
- All units, attention. Robbery in progress. - I hurt my hand. Let's go! Go!
真令人兴奋 不是吗?
That was very exciting, wasn't it?
- 他射篮了 - 飞球!
- He shoots. - Air ball.
我将要说的…
...I wanted to praise the cunningand skill you showed...
…是要表扬你们在几乎被抓到的情况下所表现出的狡猾与技巧
...in evading almost certain capture.
那是怎么回事?
What happened there?
那个傻瓜拉萨和他的队员们太过分了
That fool Lassard and his teamare getting too close.
你想让我们照顾照顾他们?
You want we shouldtake care of them?
不 把他们留给我
No. Leave them to me.
- 讨厌! - 小心 是费克勒!
- Yuck! - Watch it, it's Fackler.
当心!
Watch it!
- 我还以为我们晚点再碰面 - 赫斯特要召开一个特别会议
- Thought we weren't meeting till later. - Hurst called a special meeting.
- 关于什么? - 我有点神经紧张 哈里斯有点太高兴了
- For what? - Makes me nervous. Harris is too happy.
你也许有结论了吧?
You're probably jumping to conclusions.
- 也许我是错的 - 警官们 请坐
- I could be wrong. - Officers, be seated.
这不是什么高兴的事 所以我们就开门见山了
This is not going to be pleasant,so we'll get right to the point.
最一开始我们曾怀疑这一地区有人泄密
From the beginning, we've suspectedthat there was a leak in this precinct.
今天早上 根据秘报…
This morning,acting on an anonymous tip...
我亲自和哈里斯上尉一起搜查了你们中的一间办公室
...Captain Harris and I personallysearched one of your offices.
我恐怕我们找到了我们想要的东西
I'm afraid we foundwhat we were looking for.
这些珠宝被证实是在威尔逊·海兹一伙上次抢劫中丢失的
This jewelry has been identifiedas stolen merchandise...
上次抢劫中丢失的
...from the Wilson Heights Gang'slast robbery.
这间办公室属于埃里克·拉萨指挥官
The office belongedto Commandant Eric Lassard.
说实话 我们也很震惊
To tell the truth, we were shocked.
你震惊吗?
You're shocked?
我们别无选择 只能解除拉萨还有他的队员们的…
We have no choice but to suspendCommandant Lassard and his team...
…职务 等待调查…
...from active duty,pending an investigation...
调查
An investigation.
是的
Yes.
再见 先生们
Good day, gentlemen.
对不起 女士 噢 女士们 两位
Excuse me. And of course, lady.Ladies, two of them.
祝您日安 伟大的阁下
And good day to you, Your Excellency.
你们解散吧
You are all dismissed.
我们就是坐下来 然后什么都不做了?
We're just gonna sit hereand do nothing?
那我们怎么办? 我们被停职了
What can we do? We're suspended.
继续调查就是直接违反命令
To pursue this casewould be disobeying a direct order.
- 我们会失去工作的 - 等一下
- We can lose our jobs. - Wait a minute.
一个人被错误地指控 难道这就不值得做什么吗?
A man's being falsely accused here.Doesn't that count for anything?
她是对的 我们应该还拉萨指挥官一个清白
She's right. We've got to clearCommandant Lassard.
- 其他人不成 - 他是我们成为警察的原因
- No one else can. - He's the reason we have these jobs.
他同样也会为我们这么做的
He'd do the same for us.
说的对 我们走
You're right. Let's go.
嗯 我们在找什么?
So, what are we looking for?
我也不知道 某些线索吧
I don't know, some connection.
为什么这些抢劫全发生在51路公交以前的沿线上?
Why are these robberies taking placealong the old number 51 bus route?
这条线路有什么特别吗?
What's so special about that route?
- 我能把它调出来吗? - 当然 咱们瞧瞧
- Shall I bring it up on the screen? - Yeah, let's take a look at it.
噢 调错文件了这是城市铁路网
Oops. Wrong file.These are the intercity Railink plans.
他们肯定把旧的公交文档挪地方了
They must have moved the oldbus routes to a different file.
不不不 等一下 也许这个文件没错
No, no, no. Wait a minute.Maybe this isn't the wrong file.
你把以前的公交线路跟这个比较一下…
I'll tell you what, try cross - referencingthe old bus route...
…然后看看我们能发现什么
...against the proposed Railink systemand see what you come up with.
好的
Okay.
完全重合
It matches perfectly.
没错 但为什么威尔逊·海兹一伙只沿着铁路线抢劫呢?
Yes, but why is the Wilson Heights Gangrobbing stores along the Railink?
当城市的某一地区成为犯罪高发区的时候会怎么样呢?
What happens when a section of townbecomes a high - crime area?
- 地价下跌 - 对
- The property is devalued. - Right.
为什么有人希望如此呢?
Why would somebody wantto devalue the property?
- 他们好低价购买 - 完全正确
- So they can buy it. - Exactly.
铁路沿线的地价都很贵
The property along the Railink systemis very valuable.
现在 谁拥有这些地盘谁就会变得非常非常富有
Now, whoever owns that propertyis gonna be very, very rich.
查一下谁正在城铁沿线购地
Find out if anyone's buying propertyalong that route.
我已经在查了
I'm way ahead of you.
晚上好 先生们
Good evening, gentlemen.
今晚我们邪恶的计划终于成为了可怕的现实
Tonight our devious planbecomes a fearful reality.
我只需再发出我最后一道命令
All that remains is for meto give my final command.
开始制造混乱
Begin Operation Chaos.
你们这些家伙今晚上真是安静得可怕
You boys are awfully quiet tonight.
噢 先生 这也许是我们最后一次这么正式的跟您开会了
Oh, well, sir, this is probably goingto be our last official meeting with you.
我们想让您知道 能跟您这样的犯罪天才一起共事…
We wanted you to knowwhat a privilege it's been for us...
…真是三生有幸
...to work with a criminal geniussuch as yourself.
事实上 我们为您准备了…
As a matter of fact, we got you...
…一份微薄的礼物来表达我们对您的钦佩…
...a pathetic little something hereto express our admiration...
…对您的敬重 先生 还有我们的…
...our respect, sir, and our...
把它放到抽屉里 小子
Just put it in the drawer, boy.
是古巴货
It's Cuban.
嗯 谢谢 我真感动
I thank you. I'm touched.
哈 对我来说这才是完美的…
Why, this is the perfect way...
…庆祝胜利的方式
...for me to celebratethis victorious moment.
有趣 真有趣
Funny. Very funny.
真糟糕 我不知道密码
It's no good.I don't know the code word.
- 我打不开这个文件 - 噢 快点 我们已经很接近了
- The computer won't let me get the file. - We're so close.
我们得做点什么
We've gotta do something.
没错 先生
Yes, sir.
嘿 哥们 你真是电脑高手
Hey, brother,you really are computer friendly.
嗯 好 查一下"克莱顿·帕拉丁"
Okay. "Clayton Plating."
啊哈! 摇控炸弹
Ah - ha! Radio - controlled detonators.
炸药
Dynamite.
道格拉斯
Douglas.
- 噢 不 - 怎么了 又一个抢劫计划?
- Oh, no. - What, another robbery?
不 比那还糟
No, it's worse.
他们得到了城市的电力设计图他们要让整个城市陷入瘫痪
They've got the blueprintsand the firepower to shut the city down.
派对家伙呼叫生日男孩蜡烛已点
Party Guys to Birthday Boy.The candles are lit.
许个愿吧
Make a wish.
走吧 走 走
Come on. Come on. Come on.
你有准没有! 我要离开这!
Make up your mind.I'm out of here!
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
我们最好过去看看
We better check this out.
女士们先生们 安静一下!
Ladies and gentlemen,please just calm down.
不要惊慌 请回到座位上
There's no need to be alarmed.Just take your seats.
女士们先生们 城市警署向您隆重推荐——我
Ladies and gentlemen, the MetropolitanPolice Department proudly presents me.
哎哟!
Ow!
- 对不起 唐老鸭啊 - 呸!
- Sorry, Donald.IMITATING DONALD - Ah, phooey!
- 好了 快点 - 接着
- Okay, come on. - There you go.
- 嘿 这个轻 - 可不儿
- Hey, here comes a portable. - Yeah, right.
是的 把那个给我
Yeah, give me that one.
好
Yeah.
多美的夜晚 是吧 警官?
Nice night, isn't it, officers?
嘿 宝贝儿
Hey, baby.
摇滚就是答案 宝贝儿因为我知道你想要什么
Rock 'n' roll is the answer, baby.Because I know what you need.
因为我就要给你你想要的
Because I'm gonna give youwhat you need.
好!
Great.
非常感谢 晚安
Thank you very much. Good night.
快点 尼克 咱们走
Come on, Nick, let's go.
呼叫援助
Officers need assistance.
没电了
The batteries are dead.
你最好跑着去 现在!
You better go on foot. Now.
嗨 宝贝儿 干嘛不把枪放下?
Hey, baby.Why don't you just put that gun away.
我们一起热闹一下
Maybe we can have ourselvesa little party.
好的
Okay.
谁先来?
Who wants to go first?
看起来她用不着我们
Looks like she doesn't need us.
- 她真不赖 - 可不是
- She's good. - All right.
噢…
My...
这枪真大
What a big gun.
噢 嘿
Oh, boy, oh, boy, oh, boy.
噢 该死!
Oh, crapola!
他真是孩子气
He can be such a baby.
拉萨中士 呼叫所有人集中到加林那和麦因大街交汇处
This is Sergeant Lassard, requestingall available units to Galena and Main.
加林那和麦因大街交汇处
Galena and Main.
这边
Over here.
- 什么事? - 威尔逊一伙就在下面
- What's up? - The Wilson Heights Gang is down there.
- 怎么了? - 威尔逊一伙从这跑了
- What's the situation? - The gang is getting away.
那我们还等什么?
So, what are we waiting for?
我从车上拿点东西
I'll just get a few things from my cycle.
塔克 好了吗?
Tack, you ready?
- 好了 - 让我们去踢他们的屁股
- I'm ready. - Let's go kick some butt.
- 走! - 好的 小心点
- Let's check it out. - All right, be careful.
我要看看这隧道到底通向哪里
I'm gonna see where this tunnel goes.
瞧瞧谁来了
Look who's here.
来一个 宰一个
Here one minute, gone the next.
怎么样?
How about you?
我在想把你和你的同伴放到重金属堆里
I just thought I'd keep you company.You into heavy metal?
我要发怒了
Now I'm mad.
噢 对不起
Sorry.
你被捕了!
You're under arrest!
扔掉武器 双手放在头顶 出来!
Throw down your weaponand come out with your hands up!
我把这当作"不"!
I take that as a "no."
哈 你不成了! 我比你强!
Ha! You're weakening. I'm stronger.
没那回事 你有口臭
No, it's your breath.
- 当、当、当 - 是谁?
- Knock, knock. - Who's there?
- 布 - 布是谁?
- Boo. - Boo who?
别哭 一会儿就好
Quit crying.This will be over in a moment.
- 来啦! - 啊?
- That's it! - Huh?
我总是用一个蹩脚的笑话来结束战斗
Fighting is one thing, but bad jokesis where I draw the line.
现在就咱俩 别让那条狗掺和
This time it's you and me.Leave the dog out of it.
没问题 让我看看你有什么本事
Okay, let's see what you got.
来吧
All right.
还是飞行员哪 哈?
Airline pilot, huh?
行了,让我们来个了断
All right, let's finish it.
去死吧!
Damn you!
你到底是什么东西做的?
What the hell are you made of?
目标：人类
Target: Human.
任务：毁灭
Mission: Destroy.
上帝啊 你是个机器人!
My God, you're a robot!
"上帝啊 你是个机器人! 上帝啊 你是个机器人! "
"My God, you're a robot!My God, you're a robot!"
- 求求你 别杀我! - "求求你 别杀我! "
- Please, don't kill me! - "Please, don't kill me!"
"求求你 别杀我! "
"Please, don't kill me!"
休息吧 人类
Rest now, human.
特制大火药枪弹
Furlinger Magnum Special.
嘿 你可够棒的!
Hey, you're pretty good.
我是最棒的
I'm the best.
很可爱
Cute.
你知道 这很有趣 但我必须逮捕你
You know, this has been a lot of fun,but I have to place you under arrest.
你不会射杀…
You wouldn't shoot...
…一个手无寸铁的人吧? 不会吧?
...an unarmed man, would you?
欢迎 拉萨中士
Welcome, Sergeant Lassard.
- 你认识我? - 噢 当然了
- So you know me. - Oh, yes, indeed.
你给线人多少酬劳都是不够的
Whatever you're paying your informer,it's not enough.
你的手下让我很头疼
Your cohorts are causing mevery great annoyance.
我们聊天这会儿 我的伙计们会干掉你的朋友你
As we speak, my associatesare finishing off your friends.
现在我要干掉你
And now I'm going to finish you.
毒气?
Poison gas?
噢 行了 倒是让我歇一下
Oh, come on, give me a break.
是的 中场休息 我知道 不过很有效
Yes, melodramatic, I know,but effective.
拜拜 拉萨中士 保重
Goodbye, Sergeant Lassard,and take care.
你咳嗽地真有点让人讨厌
That's a nasty little cough you have.
那没用的
That's not gonna do it.
救命!
Help!
你还好吗?
You okay?
像你以前那样 中士
As you were, sergeant.
谢谢
Thanks.
他们的那个老大在哪?
Now, where's Mr. Big?
我们最好分开走
We better split up.
噢!
Oh!
咳…
Man...
上来吧
Come on.
找到什么了吗?
You got anything?
我想我们把他追丢了
I think we lost him.
我想我们找到他们了
I think we found him.
罪犯正向西朝铸造厂的方向逃窜
The perpetrator's attempting escape...
朝铸造厂的方向逃窜
...west on Foundry.
长官 高塔中尉正朝我们这边追捕逃犯!
Sir, Lieutenant Hightower's chasingthe perpetrator our way!
那你还在等什么? 还不快出发!
Well, what are you waiting for?Let's get out of here!
重复：向西朝铸造厂大街
Repeat: West on Foundry Street.
我正驾驶一辆征来的民用汽车进行追捕
I am pursuing in a commandeeredcivilian vehicle.
塔克!
Tack!
塔克! 琼斯!
Tack! Jones!
我抓住他了! 他在卡车里!
I got him! He's in the truck!
快追!
Come on!
有人知道这玩意儿怎么开吗?
Anybody know howto drive one of these?
当然了 先生 我度蜜月时开的就是这家伙
Affirmative, sir!We took one on our honeymoon.
都精神着点 警车一会儿就到
Y'all hang tight.Paddy wagon will be by in a minute.
一会儿见
See y'all later.
哟嗬!
Yeehaw!
我什么都没看见 学监
I don't see anything, Proctor.
这就是铸造厂大街 我听见高塔说的
Well, this is Foundry Street.I heard Hightower on the radio.
肯定是你弄错了 这儿什么事都没有
You must have been mistaken,because there is nothing going on here.
我不能相信!
I do not believe it!
说吧 别说!
Shoot. Don't say it, Proctor!
什么也别说了
Just don't say it.
- 我早说过 - 我听见了!
- Told him so. - I heard that!
我不管它去哪 我要上车
I don't care where it's going.I'm getting on.
- 你在干什么? - 让乘客上车
- What are you doing? - I'm picking up passengers.
为什么?
Why?
噢 我必须这么做 他们在我的线路上
Well, I have to, sir.They're on my route.
快开! 快! 快! 快!
Let's go! Move it, move it, move it!
快点! 动一动! 快!
Let's move! Go! Go! Go!
赶紧坐下! 开车!
Sit down! Let's go!
知不知道你在干什么?
You know what you're doing?
放松点! 我常这么干!
Relax, I do this all the time.
小心!
Look out!
欢迎上车 牛仔!
Welcome aboard, cowboy!
- 哟呼! - 呼!
- Woo - hoo! - Whoo!
他落地的时候毛病很多
He had a lot of trouble with that landing.
我给他一个九分
I'll give it a nine.
瞧着点吉恩和罗杰的水果摊!
Look out for Gene & Roger'sFruit Stand!
滚开! 你们这群疯子!
Get out of here, you maniac!
- 祝您过一个愉快的夜晚 - 是的 当然
- Have a nice evening, sir. - Yeah, sure.
你比一般的司机棒多了
You're much betterthan the regular driver.
"你比一般的司机棒多了"
"You're much betterthan the regular driver."
- 那有灯 - 没错 跟着他
- There go the lights. - All right! Let's go!
你们来这干什么?
What are you doing here?
哦…
Well...
…我们追捕罪犯来到这的 长官
...we chased the mastermindinto this office, sir.
他可不在这 快点出去找他!
Well, he isn't here.So get out there and find him!
是 长官
Yes, sir.
你在这儿干什么?
What are you doing here?
那个家伙是冒牌的!
That man is an imposter!
我?
Me?
不! 他才是假冒的!
No, he's the imposter!
让道! 让开! 让开! 赫斯特局长…
Okay, make way! Make way here!Move it, move it! Commissioner Hurst...
…他们违反了停职的规定! 我要求对他们进行处罚!
...they have violated their suspensions.I demand they be brought up on charges!
- 噢 哈里斯 闭嘴! - 噢 闭嘴 哈里斯!
- Oh, Harris, shut up! - Oh, shut up, Harris!
这两个人中有一个是罪犯的头目
Well, one of these guysis the mastermind.
但哪个是呢?
But which one?
只有一种办法可行 那就是匹诺曹测试法
There's only one sure way to find out,and that's the Pinocchio test.
这是真的 对不起 局长
That was it. Sorry, commissioner.
呼!
Whoo!
嘿 伙计们!
Hello, guys and gals!
噢 我真希望能用照相机照下你们的傻样
Oh, boy. I wish I had a pictureof your stupid faces.
市长先生!
Mr. Mayor!
你好 哈里斯 你这个白痴
Hello, Harris, you stupid twit!
谢谢你向我提供的情报 它们可真有用
Thank you for all the info when you weretrying to catch me. I found it so useful.
呜呼!
Woo - hoo!
是哈里斯泄的秘
Harris was the leak?
我不知道! 我是说 他是市长 我的意思是…
I didn't know!I mean, he was the mayor. I mean...
- 我怎么会知道? - 为什么?
- How was I supposed to know? - Why?
为了钱 长官
For money, sir.
他知道城铁沿线的地段很值钱
He knew property along theRailink route would be very valuable.
所以他组织这伙人让这些地段的地价下跌…
So he had his gang set up a crime waveto devalue the property...
…这样他就能低价购入
...so he could buy it up, cheap.
再加上电力中断所造成的破坏 他就能拥有全部这些地段
With the damage that blackout caused,well, he was gonna own it all.
他坐在幕后 停止这些犯罪活动…
He'd just sit back,stop the crime wave...
…等退休后就看着他的这些地段不断升值
...retire from public serviceand watch his property skyrocket.
你是说这一切都是房地产的诡计?
You mean this was alljust a real - estate scam?
十亿美元的房地产诡计 长官
A billion - dollar real - estate scam, sir.
嘻嘻
Hee!
把他带走!
Take him away.
把我带走? 噢 真是粗鲁无礼! 呼!
Take me away? Oh, how rude!How rude! Whoo!
把你自己带走! 你试试!
Take yourselves away. Try that!
事实上 你们被解雇了! 你们每一个人 全被解雇了!
As a matter of fact, you're all fired.Each and every one of you is fired. Fired!
别碰我的航模! 你们谁都不许碰!
And don't you touch my model ships!Not one of you!
不许碰他们! 这些精巧的小家伙们
Don't touch them!The little men are so delicate.
你们又大又粗的指头会把它们碾碎!
They'll crumblebetween your big, fat fingers!
警察的大粗手指头!
Your big cop fingers!
埃里克 我该向您和您的队员们道歉我真是个傻瓜
Eric, I owe you and the team an apology.I've been a fool.
是的
Yes.
不过没关系 局长
But that's all right, commissioner.
恢复您和您队员们的职务
Consider yourselfand your team reinstated.
太棒了!
All right!
我很荣幸授予这些警官…
And so it is with great honorthat I award these men and women...
…杰出荣誉勋章 以表彰他们在城市危难的时刻所做出的一切
...the Distinguished Service Medalfor serving this city in its hour of need.
女士们先生们 我们光荣的警官们
Ladies and gentlemen,our honored police officers.
我想坐你的椅子 中尉
I think I'll take your seat, lieutenant.
你坐我的椅子
You take mine.
是的 先生
Yes, sir.
除非它有什么毛病
Unless there's some problem.
不 没有
Nope. No problem.
噢…
Oh...
学监
Proctor.
噢 学监!
Oh, Proctor.
学监!
Proctor!